这是三分熟  这是五分熟  快去上菜
This one's rare. This one's mediumwell. Go, go, go!
菲比  晚餐好吃吗
Hey, Phoebe! How was dinner?!
晚餐很好吃  我只是来打招呼  我要走了
Dinner was good! Just saying hi! Now I'm gonna go!
你好啊
Well, hello there.
我在菜单上没看到这道美味
I didn't see this on the menu.
提姆  她是菲比
Tim, this is Phoebe.
菲比  他是新来的副厨师长提姆
Phoebe, this is Tim, my new sous chef.
你是莫妮卡的老板  不  她是我的老板
So you're Monica's boss?  No, she's my boss.
"副"在法文里是"之下"的意思
"Sous" is French for "under."
我副（明）白了
I "sousstand."
提姆  我要一份乌贼跟一份凯撒沙拉
Tim, I need a calamari and a caesar salad.
你可以把青酱递给我吗
And could you get me the pesto?
青酱是你做的吗  没错
You made pesto?  Yes, I did.
你觉得你的青酱是最"棒"的吗
Would you say your pesto is the besto?
我不知道  我会说它真的很"强"
I don't know. I would say it's pretty goodo.
别忘了给我拿乌贼跟沙拉
I still need the calamari and salad.
我喜欢你的项链
I like your necklace.
这是我自己做的  你真的好有天份
I made it myself.  You are so talented.
还是不够"酱"
Well, it's no pesto.
我们就别兜圈子了
Alright, alright. Let's just cut to the chase.
你是单身  你也单身
Okay. You're single. You're single.
他11点下班  她会等你的电话
He gets off work at 11. She'll be waiting for your call.
我会把你的电话号码给他
I'll give him your number if I could just get
只要你给我乌贼跟凯撒沙拉
one calamari and one caesar salad!
我没有大叫  我不必被罚一块钱
I did not yell. I am not putting a dollar in the jar.
《老友记》  第八季  第5集  瑞秋的约会
Friends S08E05 The One With Rachel's Date
宾  你还在熬夜加班
Wow, Bing! Burning the midnight oil.
你很了解我的  老板
You know me, sir.
我正好有个问题问你
I do have a question for you.
你知道要怎么避开公司的电脑网路
Do you know how I can get around the office computer network...
看劲爆火辣的国际黄片吗
...so I can access the really good Internet porn?
你真爱开玩笑  宾
You're a joker, Bing.
那有什么好笑的
What's funny about that?
抱歉让你等这么久
Sorry I kept you waiting so long.
没关系  你想去哪里
That's okay. Where do you wanna go?
我以为你知道我要去哪里
I think you know where I wanna go.
硬石餐厅  对
The Hard Rock Cafe?  Yeah.
又要去  对
Again?  Yeah.
我真的很喜欢那里的食物
I'm telling you, I like the food.
你是喜欢那里的紫雨展示品
You like the Purple Rain display.
巴伯  托比  祝你今晚玩得开心
Hey, Bob.  Hey, Toby. Have a good night.
那家伙叫你托比
Did that guy just call you Toby?
对  他以为那是我的名字
Yeah, he thinks that's my name.
你为什么不更正他
Why don't you correct him?
现在纠正有点太晚了
It's been going on way too long now.
他第一次这么叫我  我们只是在走廊擦肩而过
The first time he said it, we were just passing each other in the hallway,
所以我什么都没说
so I didn't say anything.
第二次他说"托比  你要吃甜甜圈吗"
The next time he said, "Hey, Toby, want a doughnut?"
我确实想吃甜甜圈
I wanted the doughnut.
五年后甜甜圈早就消化光了 我还是托比
Five years later, the doughnut's gone and I'm still Toby.
五年了  钱德勒  你得告诉他
Five years. Chandler, you have to tell him.
不行  那多尴尬啊
No. That would be so awkward.
再说  我们不在同一个楼层工作  他在六楼
Besides, we don't work together. He's on the sixth floor.
他只是偶尔才会叫我一次托比  没什么
So he calls me Toby once in a while. What's the big deal?
这已经算不错了  反正他不是叫我妙丽
It could be worse. It's not like he's calling me Muriel.
妙丽  他为什么要叫你妙丽
Muriel. Why would he call you Muriel?
天啊
Oh, my God.
钱德勒·M·宾
Chandler "M." Bing.
那不仅是个M  你的中间名是妙丽
It's not just an "M." Your middle name is Muriel!
那是家族名字
It is a family name.
钱德勒·妙丽·宾
Chandler Muriel Bing.
你父母真是完全不给你留活路  对吧
Your parents never even gave you a chance, did they?
德瑞克  我找出你丧失记忆的原因了
Drake, I've discovered the reason for your memory loss.
为什么
What is it?
你的脑部移植手术并未完全成功
Apparently your brain transplant was not entirely successful.
你的身体在排斥洁西卡的脑部
It seems your body's rejecting Jessica's brain.
很严重吗
Is it serious?
如果我们可以从捐赠者的身体抽取组织...
Not if we extract tissue from the original body...
合成抗体  将其导入你体内
...and synthesize antibodies and introduce them to your system
以此来解除排异效应
which could stop you from rejecting the brain.
听起来很简单  我们就按你说的做吧
That sounds simple enough. Let's just do that.
我们可以那么做
We would,
但我们想挖出洁西卡的尸体时
but when we went to exhume Jessica's body...
发现它不见了
...it was gone.
卡
Cut.
非常不错  大伙们
Very nice, people.
我换好衣服后  我们就可以去吃晚餐了
Okay, let me just get changed and we can go to dinner.
洁西卡的尸体怎么了
What happened to Jessica's body?
我不能剧透  你得看电视才会知道
I'm not telling you. You'll have to see it on TV.
你不知道  对吧  对  我也不在乎
You don't know, do you?  No. couldn't care less.
你表现得很好  你也是
Good scene, man.  You too.
怎么  你根本不是演员
What? You weren't in it.
凯许  她是我朋友瑞秋
Kash, this is my friend Rachel.
二位互相认识一下
Rachel, Kash. Kash, Rachel.
为什么之前我没有见过你
Why haven't I seen you here before?
乔伊觉得我会丢他的脸
Joey just thinks I'll embarrass him.
他认为我是肥皂剧脑残粉
He thinks I'm a soap opera nut.
我才不是  真的
Which I'm not. I'm not.
虽然我的确知道
Although, I do know
你最喜欢胡桃奶油口味的冰淇淋
your favorite ice cream flavor is butter pecan.
你的狗叫华利
And your dog's name is Wally.
天啊  我在摸你的胳膊  我们走吧
Look, I'm just stroking your arm.  Here we go. Here we go.
再见  凯许  再见
Bye, Kash.  Bye.
帮我跟华利问好
Say hi to Wally.
莫妮卡
Monica.
昨晚我跟提姆玩得很开心
Oh, my god. I had the best time with Tim last night.
他真的很体贴
He is so sweet.
我等不及钻到他的身体"下"面去
I can't wait to get "sousneath" him.
我得开除他  为什么
I have to fire him.  Why?
他很不称职  动作超慢  还会把食物烧焦
He's terrible. He's slow. He burns things.
昨晚他还把我的甜点主厨烧着了
Last night he lit my pastry chef on fire.
他可能是太紧张了  你老是凶巴巴的
Maybe he was just nervous. You can be intimidating.
我见过你的甜点主厨
Besides,  I've met your pastry chef,
她牛哄哄的  也该灭灭她的威风了
and she can stand to be taken down a peg or two.
现在她没有眉毛了  任务完成
Well, now she has no eyebrows. Mission accomplished.
莫妮卡  他热爱他的工作
But, Monica, he loves his job so much.
你不能再给他一次机会吗  拜托
Can't you just give him another chance, please?
好吧  但如果他再放火烧别人  他非走不可
All right. But if he lights someone else on fire, he's out of there.
那很公平  谢谢你
That's fair. Thank you so much. Thanks.
看起来他烧甜点主厨的时候
Oops. Looks like when he got the pastry chef,
也烧到你了
he got you a little bit too.
我这是花钱去做的头发
I paid to have this done.
我喜欢
Love it!
知道吗  凯许真的喜欢你
Hey. You know, Kash really liked you the other day.
他觉得你很迷人
He said he thought you were charming.
我以为自己蠢到家了  我站在你这边
I thought I was a complete idiot.  I'm with you.
他还问我你会不会愿意跟他约会
He even asked me if I thought you'd go out with him.
我感觉快要吐了
I think I'm gonna throw up a little.
你怎么说  我说不会
What did you say?  I said, "No."
什么
What?
我觉得既然你怀孕了
What? I just figured since you're pregnant,
就不会跟别人约会了
you're not gonna be seeing people.
乔伊
Okay, Joey.
首先  他是凯许·福特  不是一般人
First of all, Kash Ford? Not people.
其次  你告诉他我怀孕了  他说了什么
Second of all, what did he say when you told him I was pregnant?
我没告诉他  我不确定你要不要告诉别人
I didn't tell him. I didn't know if you're telling people.
那时候我以为凯许只是"一般人"
This back when I thought Kash was still "people."
很好  别告诉他
Good, good. Don't tell him. Don't tell him.
让他打电话给我
Just have him call me, okay?
瑞秋  我觉得这样不...
Rach, look. I really don't think that's such a great...
照我的话做  不然我会回到摄影棚
Okay. You go do it or I'll come back to that set.
泡其他的男演员  一个都不放过
I'll meet more actors. I'll meet them all.
巴伯  我朋友托比今天还好吗
Hey, Bob.  How's my pal Toby doing today?
我看到他时会帮你问一下
If I see him, I'll ask.
你刚刚在跟六楼的巴伯说话吗
Was that Bob from six you were just talking to?
对  你们互相认识
Yeah.  Then you know each other?
我们知道彼此的名字而已
We're on a semifirstname basis.
如果他加入我们的团队呢  巴伯吗
What do you think of adding him to our team?  Bob?
每天跟我们在这里一起工作
Working here with us? Every day?
我不知道他有没有那个能耐
Yeah. I don't know if he has what it takes.
是吗  六楼的人很喜欢他
Really? They love him down on six.
但这里是11楼
But this is 11.
这里的工作要难上两倍
It's almost twice as hard up here.
好吧  我明白你的意思了
Okay, I hear you loud and clear.
巴伯还是不能调职  我想那样最好
Bob will stay put.  I think it's best, sir.
但我们真的急需新鲜血液
But we really do need to find someone up here.
工作开始越积越多了
Work is starting to pile up.
我桌上的文件已经叠到这么高了
I've got a stack of documents on my desk this high.
我给你出个主意  把它们丢到碎纸机里
You know what we should do. Just toss them in the shredder
就说你从来没有收到它们
and claim you never got them.
那真的很好笑  宾
That's a good one, Bing.
我该怎么做他们才会觉得我是认真的
What does a guy have to do to be taken seriously around here?
我又给了他一次机会  但提姆非走不可
Okay, I gave him another chance, but Tim has got to go.
但...  不行  他太不称职了
But...  No, no, no. He is totally incompetent.
我打电话给推荐他给我的厨师
I called the chef who recommended him to me.
他说"哈哈  整到你了"
He said, "Ha, ha! Gotcha!"
但别今天开除他  为什么
Okay, okay. But you can't fire him today.  Why not?
因为今天我要甩掉他
Because I'm dumping him today.
什么  你说他很体贴
What? You said he was so sweet.
他确实体贴  但也太体贴了
He is sweet. He's too sweet.
老是打电话给我
He calls me all the time.
"你平安回家了吗
"Did you get home from work okay?
你洗澡没出事吧"
Did you get out of the shower okay?"
别接电话不就得了  那他会亲自过来
Just don't pick up your phone.  Then he comes over!
"我好担心你"  有点男子气概吧
"I was so worried about you." Be a man!
所以现在我不能开除他
So now I'm not allowed to fire him?
我们不能让他在同一天既失业又失恋
We can't fire him and dump him on the same day.
他会自杀的
He'll kill himself.
那我今天开除他
Okay, well then, I'll fire him today,
你再跟他交往一星期
and you go out with him another week.
你开什么玩笑  再跟他交往一个星期
Are you kidding? Another week with that simp,
我会自杀的
I'll kill myself.
我们都在今天跟他摊牌  让他自己想办法应付
Okay, then we'll both do it today and he'll just have to deal with it.
好吧  但问题是谁要先说呢
Okay. But the question is who's gonna go first?
后说的就是贱人
Whoever goes second is the bitch.
什么意思  开除刚失恋的员工
What do you mean?   Come on, fire a guy that's just been dumped?
贱人  甩掉刚失业的恋人
Bitch! And dump a guy that's just been fired?
金发贱人
Blond bitch!
我几天前就想开除他  所以应该让我先说
I wanted to do this days ago, so I think I should go first.
好吧  你说得有理
All right, that makes sense.
去你的  我要先说
But screw you! I'm going first!
托比  你有空吗  当然  什么事
Toby, you got a sec?  Sure. What's up?
我们刚开完会
I just had a meeting.
我本想被调职到这里来
I was actually hoping to get transferred up here,
但刚发现我的美梦破灭了
but I just found out it's not gonna happen.
很明显有人认为我不是"11楼的材料"
Apparently somebody thinks I'm not "11 thfloor material."
钱德勒到底是谁
Say, who the hell is this Chandler?
今晚约会时哪个藉口
What do you think is a better excuse
最适合我用来挡酒
for why I'm not drinking on this date tonight?
"我正在戒酒"  "我是摩门教徒"
"I'm a recovering alcoholic," "I'm a Mormon"...
或是"我昨晚喝太醉现在还在宿醉"
...or "I got so hammered last night I'm still a little drunk"?
今晚你要做什么
So, what do you want to do tonight?
安杰丽卡有部很棒的乌克兰电影上映
There’s a Ukrainian film at the Angelica
听说很震撼人心  你想看吗
that's supposed to be very powerful. Interested?
没兴趣
No. No.
但我可以陪你看一般人看的电影
But I'll go see a normalperson movie with you.
瑞秋  你要一起来吗
Rach, you wanna come?
不行  我有约会
Oh, no. I can't. I've got a date.
约会  对  怎么了  很奇怪吗
A date?  Yeah. Why, is that weird for you?
不  一点都不奇怪  那很正常
Why, no. It's the opposite of weird. It's regular.
太普通了  事实上还有点无聊
It's mundane. It's actually a little dull.
它可不是乌克兰电影
It's no Ukrainian film.
耳环
Earrings!
她有约会  对象是谁
A date? She's got a date? With who?
我撮合她跟一个男演员
I set her up with this actor on my show.
是你帮她牵的红线  不是
You set her up?  No.
乔伊  你在想什么
Joey, what were you thinking?
我觉得应该没关系
I was thinking that it would probably be okay...
因为你们两个已经分手五年了
because Ross hasn’t gone out with Rachel in five years!
乔伊  我担心不是她  而是我的宝宝
Joey, I'm not worried about her! I'm worried about my baby.
跟她约会的人  也在跟我的宝宝约会
Whoever she dates, my baby dates.
这个"男演员"要带她去哪里
Where is this "actor" taking them?
我也是"男演员"
Hey! I'm an "actor" too.
他们大概要搭渡轮
I'm not sure. I think they're taking the ferry
到史坦顿岛玩
out to some Italian place on Staten Island.
渡轮  我的宝宝要搭渡轮
A ferry? My baby's going on a ferry?
你知道那有多危险吗
Do you have any idea how dangerous those are?
渡轮是指那种载车的
Are we talking about one of those big boats
速度缓慢的大船吧
that carry cars that go like five miles an hour?
他们为什么不去跳飞机  那多有意思
Why not just jump out of an airplane. Thatthat's a fun date!
或点火柴把彼此烧了  也很有意思
or burn each other with matches? That's fun, too.
乔伊  凯许  罗斯  他就是凯许
Hey, Joey.  Hey, Kash. This is Ross. Ross, this is Kash.
我听说今晚你们要去搭渡轮
Hey, I hear you're going on a ferry tonight.
你挺大胆啊
Bit of a daredevil, are we?
这件裙子是不是太露了  嗨   凯许
Do you guys think this is too slutty? Hi, Kash.
瑞秋  你准备好了吗
Hey, Rachel. You ready to go?
是的  待会见  好
Yeah. See you guys later.  Okay.
祝你们玩的愉快  谢谢
Have a great time, you guys.  Thank you.
那件裙子的确太露了
And yes, it is too slutty!
我很高兴你打电话给我
I'm so glad you called.
感觉之前一直是我打给你
I feel like it's always me calling you.
什么事  菲比没事吧
So, what's up? Is everything okay with Phoebe?
我待会就会没事
It will be in a minute. Listen.
提姆  你真的很棒
Tim, you're a really great guy.
那是因为我跟你在一起
That's because I'm with you.
但我的人生现在走到了...
It's just, I'm in a place in my life right now where...
抱歉  "刚刚有消息传过来"
So sorry. "This just in."
是餐厅有急事呼我  莫妮卡要我马上赶过去
Oh, it's 911 from the restaurant, that means Monica needs me right away.
不是的  我知道发生了什么事
No, she doesn't! I know what that is.
你可以留下来
You can stay.
我也会想你的  菲比
I'll miss you too, Pheebs.
我会把你放在这里
And I will be holding you right here.
你想看哪部电影
So, what movie do you wanna see?
我不想看那种得认真看字幕的电影
And not one I have to read, okay?
我受够看书了
I get that from books.
书  好吧  汽车杂志  玉米片包装
Books?  Alright, car magazines, cereal boxes...
但那就够我受的了
...but it's enough!
我们别去看电影了
I tell you what. Why don't we just stay here?
就待在家里玩吧
Let's not see a movie, we'll just and hang.
你要等瑞秋约会回来吗
Just wait for Rachel to come back from her date?
如果你想那么做的话  我不会反对
Hey, if that's what you wanna do, I'm not gonna say no.
哥们  你这是怎么了
Dude, what is going on?
我得知道他们约会进行得怎样  为什么
I have to find out how it went.  Why?
他可能是我孩子的继父
This guy could be my baby's stepfather.
才约会一次  你就担心他们要结婚了
They go on one date and you're worried about them getting married?!
他又不是你
He's not you!
我不敢相信她去约会了
I just... I can't believe she's dating!
罗斯  你觉得她该怎么做呢
Ross, what did you think she was gonna do?
我不知道
I don't know.
我不敢相信会发生这种事
I guess I just can't believe any of this is happening.
你是什么意思
What do you mean?
我以为我再生个孩子
It's just I always thought when I had another kid,
情况会不一样
it'd be different.
我爱本
I love Ben.
但每次送他到卡罗尔跟苏珊家
But every time  I drop him off at Carol and Susan's...
我都会觉得很伤心
...it breaks my heart a little.
我一直想像着  我跟未来的太太周末躺在床上
I've always had this picture of me and my next wife in bed on Sunday,
我的孩子跑过来跳到床上
my kid comes running in, leaps up on the bed
我们会一起看报纸
and we all read the paper together, you know?
或许还会抢着看科学版
Maybe fight over the science section.
很棒啊  你现在还是有机会过那样的生活
That's a nice picture. You can still have that.
不  瑞秋跟别的男人约会去了
No. No, I can't. Rachel's out with some guy.
我的孩子跟她一起去了
My baby went with her.
那个梦想只会离我越来越远了
If anything, that picture keeps moving further away.
我能问你一件事吗
Hey, can I ask you something?
你想像你未来太太的时候
In this picture of you and your wife,
她是瑞秋吗
is your wife Rachel?
以前是的
It used to be.
现在我梦里的人没有具体的相貌
Now she doesn't really have a face.
但她的身材超火辣
Smokin body, though.
说得好  但是罗斯  她已经不是瑞秋了
Good call. But the face, Ross, the face isn't Rachel.
对  但如果是的话  事情会简单很多吧
No. But how much easier would it be if it were?
我懂  但那不是她要的生活
Yeah, I know, but I don't think that's not what she wants.
那也不是我想要的生活
No, it's not what I want either.
我不能逼自己再爱上她
I mean II can't force myself to fall in love with her again now.
罗斯  或许你需要新的展望
Okay, Ross, maybe you need a new picture, okay?
它会跟你之前的梦想不一样
It won't be what you thought.
但不论如何...
But no matter what...
你都将迎来一个新的生命  你的孩子
...there's gonna be a brandnew little baby. Your baby.
谁在乎梦想是什么样的呢
Who cares what the picture looks like?
对
Yeah.
我们一起出去找点乐子吧
I tell you what. Let's you and me go out and have some fun.
你想做什么都行  来吧
Whatever you want. Come on.
我们还赶得上看乌克兰电影
We can catch that Ukrainian film.
不  我说找乐子
No, I said fun.
嘿  托比  嘿  巴比
Hey, Toby?  Hey, Bobby.
事实上是巴伯
It's Bob, actually.
你在这里工作  钱德勒·宾的办公室在哪里
You work up here. Can you tell me where this Chandler Bing's office is?
就在...
Yeah, it's right...
就在那里  你问这个做什么
Right there. Let me ask you, why?
我想找那个混蛋谈谈
I wanna talk to that bastard,
看他跟我有什么过节
See what his problem is.
好吧  巴伯  听我说
Okay, Bob. Listen.
是我害你无法调职
I'm the reason you didn't get the job up here.
托比  不要  巴伯
Toby, don't.  Bob.
托比  别替他背黑锅了
Toby, I'm not gonna let you cover for him.
你说任何话只会让我更气钱德勒
Anything you say will just get me more upset with Chandler.
那还真是让我进退两难
That puts me in a difficult position.
我收到你的寻呼了  没事吧
I got your page. Is everything okay?
那得视情况而定
That depends.
你跟菲比还好吧
How are you and Phoebe?
很好  谢谢你介绍我们认识
Oh it's great! It's great! Thank you so much for introducing us!
这是我的荣幸
My pleasure.
好吧  我得跟你宣布一个坏消息
Okay, I'm afraid I've got some bad news.
菲比  莫妮卡
Phoebe!  Monica!
你被开除了  我要跟你分手
You're fired!  I'm breaking up with you!
什么
What?
我要跟你分手
I'm breaking up with you.
你被开除了  为什么
You're fired.  Why?
抱歉  我还没有准备好跟别人长期交住
I'm sorry. I'm not ready for a relationship right now.
我也很抱歉  但我喜欢凡事照我的方法来做
I'm sorry too. But I like things done a certain way.
我们之间的化学反应不对
The chemistry's just not right.
这个理由很好  我们也是一样
Oh that's good, the chemistry thing for us too.
好吧
Wow. Okay.
我知道我大黏人了
I realize I came on a little strong,
那是因为我觉得你很棒
but it's because I think you're so amazing.
我要告诉你
I just wanna tell you how much
我很感激你给我这个机会
I appreciate you giving me an opportunity here.
你是我合作过最有天份的厨师
because you're the most talented chef I've ever worked for.
总之...
Anyway...
提姆  等一下  什么事
Tim, wait.  Yeah?
我话说得太快了  这份工作需要时间学习
I think I spoke too quickly. There's a learning curve with this job.
或许我们可以再试一次
And maybe we could try it again.
真的吗  是的
Really?  Yeah.
谢谢  我知道我可以表现得更好  好
Thank you so much. I know I can be better.  Okay.
提姆  我只想说祝你好运
And, Tim, I just want to say good luck here.
你好  嗨
Hello.  Hi.
你约会情况如何
How was the date?
我现在孤身一人  还买了15块钱的糖果
I'm alone and I just bought $ 15 wonth of candy bars.
你觉得呢
What do you think?
发生了什么事
What happened?
我不知深浅地告诉他我怀孕了
I made the mistake of telling him I was pregnant.
他不能接受吗  他的反应比你强
He didn't take it so well?  Well, better than you.
但那还不是我想要的反应
But still not what you want.
对  他变得举止怪异  语无伦次
Yeah. He got all weird and sputtery.
然后他说"我听说长痔疮很烦人的"
Then he said: "I hear those hemorrhoids are a bitch."
他听着很镇静  是吧
He sounds swell.  Doesn't he?
我给你讲点好笑的事情吧  好啊
You want a little cheering up?  Yeah.
坐下  好
Sit down.  Okay.
你猜谁的中间名叫妙丽
Guess whose middle name is Muriel.
钱德勒·M·宾  天啊
Chandler M. Bing. Oh, my God.
我很遗憾你的约会没有成功  没事的
I'm sorry about your date.  It's all right.
我猜我受够了约会
I guess I'm just done with the whole dating thing.
那只是我生命中另一个翻天覆地的变化
Just one more thing in my life that's suddenly completely different.
这真的很难  我了解
This is hard.  Yeah, I know.
但反过来说
On the other hand,
再过七个月你就要拥有一个宝宝了
in about seven months you're gonna have something...
你对他的爱
...that you're gonna love
胜于你对任何约会对象的感觉
more than any guy you've ever gone out with.
等着吧
Just wait.
等到孩子第一次抓住你的手指
Wait until the first time your baby grabs your finger.
那种感觉妙极了
You have no idea.
谢谢你  亲爱的
Thanks, sweetie.
你要喝杯咖啡吗
You wanna grab some coffee?
不  我要回家吃掉10根棒棒糖
No. I'm gonna go eat 10 candy bars.
我还以为我让你心情变好了
I thought I cheered you up.
没错  我一共买了20根呢  是啊
You did. There are 20 in here.  Right.
晚安  晚安
Good night.  Good night.
罗斯  是我
Ross?  Yeah?
我是蒙娜  我们在婚礼上见过
Hey, it's Mona. From the wedding.
你好吗
How are you?
我很好  但你欠我一只舞
I'm good, except you owe me a dance.
没错
That's right.
你想看乌克兰电影吗
Well, would you be interested in seeing a Ukrainian film?
你是认真的  好吧
Oh, you're serious. Sure.
太棒了
Great. Well...
我想再来一杯咖啡
I think I need one more cup of coffee.
没问题  我去帮你买  好
Sure, let me get it for you.  Okay.
谨以此片纪念理查德·L·考克斯一世（柯特妮·考克斯, 莫妮卡扮演者的父亲）
巴伯
Bob?
Bob!
巴伯
你到底在做什么
What the hell are you doing?
我刚发现这是钱德勒的办公室
I just find out this is Chandler's office.
来吧  托比  快来帮我
Come on, Toby. Give me a hand!